Contact

tinarn1@icloud.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tina-mond-fnp-c (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Family Medicine

Office Procedures

Advanced Suturing

Certifications

Registered Nurse - Illinois

Family Nurse Practitioner - Missouri/ Illinois

Registered Nurse - Missouri

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau International Honor Society

Tina Mond

MSN, APRN, FNP-C at SIHF Healthcare Doctoral Student Greater St. Louis Area

Summary

MSN, APRN, FNP-C

*Dual Licensed (MO and IL)

Physician/FNP-guided clinical practicum.

Motivated, self-developing and adaptable nursing professional combines 29 years of clinical nursing experience with compassion to meet the challenges facing today's healthcare organizations. A clear awareness of diverse backgrounds, alert to widely varied patient needs and populations. Skilled regarding advanced care with a strong emphasis on physical assessment, collaborating with providers, administration and documentation of primary care, ensuring patient safety, and delivering quality patient care. Extensive successful background within fast-paced environments i.e..,

Progressive Care Units, Telemetry, PACUs, Hemodialysis, Women's Health Clinics, Eye Surgery Centers and a wide variation of specialty Intensive Care Units. Physician guided clinical experience in Internal Medicine and Pediatric Primary Care.

Currently: Managing patients as their Primary Care Provider of chronic and acute illnesses specializing in Family Practice, Pediatrics and Women's Health.

Experience

SIHF Healthcare

1 year 10 months

MSN, APRN, FNP-C

November 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months)

Saint Louis, Metro-East (Illinois)

Family Practice of Medicine

Primary Care Provider to the underserved of Metro East of Saint Louis, MO

RN, MSN, APRN, FNP-C

October 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Greater Saint Louis Area

Travel Registered Nurse. Extensive Critical Care background. Assignments in Medical/Surgical/Trauma/Transplant/Neuro/Cardiovascular ICUs, PCUs, PACUs, ACLS Telemetry, MMS Telemetry, Women's Health Clinics and Eye Surgery Centers.

**Facilities:

*8-13 Week contracts with extensions up to the 1 yr maximum in some facilities.

Northwestern Memorial Hospital

Saint Louis University Hospital

Missouri University Hospital

Christian Hospital

St. Anthony's Medical Center

Blessing Hospital

Barnes Jewish Hospital

St. John's Hospital

Carbondale Memorial Hospital

St. Clare Surgery Center

Florissant Eye Surgery Center

Hillsboro Area Hospital

Infertility Center of Saint Louis

Barnes-Jewish Hospital Staff Registered Nurse July 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 6 months)

Greater St. Louis Area

Largest ICU in the Nation, Staff RN in Surgical/Burn/Trauma unit. Management of high acuity patients, Management of Credentialed IV infusions, Management of CVVHD and hemodynamics monitoring devices. Phlebotomy, ABG draws and interpretation, Family and patient education, Care and management of ventilated patients, Interdisciplinary Team meetings. Primary care in a teaching hospital. Collaboration with physicians, residents an fellows.

Decatur Memorial Hospital
Staff Registered Nurse III
September 2007 - November 2013 (6 years 3 months)
Decatur, Illinois

Staff Registered Nurse in Medical/Surgical ICU; Charge RN; Resource RN, Delegation of tasks to allied health professionals, Management of sepsis pts, Management of high acuity patients over extended periods.

Fresenius Medical Care North America Charge Registered Nurse September 2006 - September 2007 (1 year 1 month) Decatur, Illinois

Administration and management of Hemodialysis Treatments; Lab review and determination of treatment, Supervision of allied health professionals

Provena Health
Staff Registered Nurse
July 2005 - September 2006 (1 year 3 months)
Urbana-Champaign, Illinois Area

Administration of care to high acuity patients in the Medical, Cardiovascular and Cath Lab units. Hemodynamic Monitoring, Primary Care, Management of post heart cath pts, Blood Draws, X-ray Interpretation, Management of Continuous Credentialed IV Meducations

Decatur Memorial Hospital Staff Registered Nurse I June 2004 - June 2005 (1 year 1 month) Decatur, Illinois

Primary Care to high acuity pts in the Cardiovascular ICU. Management of CVVHD, Recovery of postoperative Coronary Artery Bypass Grafting pts, CHF patients, Chest pain, Arrythmias and many other conditions.

Education

Chamberlain University
MSN, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2015 - 2018)

Millikin University
BSN, Nursing Science (2004 - 2006)

Richland Community College ADN, Nursing Science · (2000 - 2004)

Heartland Technical Academy (Formerly Decatur Area Vocational Center)

Nursing Diploma, Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse Training · (1989 - 1991)